<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Services>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Paternity Establishment</Name>
			<Details>Paternity means fatherhood. Establishing paternity creates a legal relationship between a
				 father and a child. Establishing parentage for a child provides that child many potential benefits.Information for parents: If you are a parent who needs to
				 establish paternity for your child, click here. On the FAQ page, search for topic Child Support-Information for Parents.
				 Information for providers: If you are a hospital employee, midwife, or other entity which provides parents an opportunity to sign a paternity acknowledgment,
				 click here. On the FAQ page, search for topic Child Support-Information for Providers.
			</Details>
	 </ServiceBO>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Establishing Support Order</Name>
			<Details>Administrative - DCS will establish support administratively using the Washington State
				 Child Support Schedule when any of the following are true:
				 1.	New! July 2012 - Notice and Finding of Financial Responsibility
				 2.	There is no court order or administrative support order in any jurisdiction.
				 3.	The court order is silent about the non-custodial parent paying support.
				 4.	The court order does not set support as a fixed amount, but the amount is determinable.
				 5.	The non-custodial father has a valid acknowledgement of paternity on file with a state.
				 Learn more about how DCS establishes administrative orders. If you think that current child support on your administrative order should change because
				 circumstances have changed, contact DCS. A modification may be appropriate.
				 Learn more about administrative order modification.
			</Details>
	 </ServiceBO>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Modifying Support Orders</Name>
			<Details>If DCS is not enforcing your child support or you want to modify your order without a DCS review:
				 •	Contact your attorney to modify the order, or
				 •	You may do it yourself, by using the '"'Pro Se'"' method.
				 Packets are available at any DCS office. Some counties have court facilitators to assist you.
				 If you do not have a case with DCS, but you want DCS to review your order, you may apply for full collection services and request a review for modification.
				 Is there already a child support order?
				 If DCS is enforcing your child support order, you may ask DCS to review your order to see if a modification is appropriate, or you may petition for
				 modification without DCS's help.
			</Details>
	 </ServiceBO>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Enforcement or Collection</Name>
			<Details>DCS will provide current support services until the child emancipates, leaves the custodian's	household, or goes to live with the non-custodial parent. DCS will continue to collect support arrears unless the parties reconcile.
			</Details>
	 </ServiceBO>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Termination of Support</Name>
			<Details>DCS will provide current support services until the child emancipates, leaves the custodian's	household, or goes to live with the non-custodial parent. DCS will continue to collect support arrears unless the parties reconcile.
			</Details>
	</ServiceBO>
			<Name>Employers</Name>
			<Details>As employers in Washington, you do so much to help families in need of child support. You withhold support from
				 earnings and send it to DCS. You enroll children in health insurance plans. You report your newly hired and rehired employees. You answer our inquiries when
				 we need to find a parent or need income information. You even deduct support for families in other states.
			</Details>
	 <ServiceBO>
			<Name>Apply for Services</Name>
			<Details>First decide which application package below fits your circumstances and then download all of the associated
				 forms for that selection.
				 Mail your completed application to the following address:
				 Division of Child Support
				 Central Services
				 P.O. Box 11520
				 Tacoma, Washington 98411-5520
				 Once you send in your application, send any child support payments you receive to the Washington State Support Registry. DCS must have a physical record of
				 all payments made by the non-custodial parent. Send one application for each noncustodial parent.
			</Details>
	</ServiceBO>
	 <ServiceBO>	
			<Name>Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)</Name>
			<Details>https://www.dshs.wa.gov/esa/faq
			</Details>
	 </ServiceBO>
</Services>



